You must have come to know that roti, kapda and makaan is the
name of an old film and our
old basic needs are below, yes it has changed,
no what is roti, kapda, makaan and
insurance, but maybe I will tell you if you do
n't know then you must have come to know now, if I
talk about why basic needs have become, yes in
today's time because in today's time the
disease that is spreading, corona virus or
any other disease, if a common man gets
treatment in a good private hospital then it costs a lot, it
costs in lakhs, so if his bank
balance is not so good then he gets
treatment by taking a loan, all three of his roti, kapda and makaan are
not protected, then
if we talk about his good
insurance, health insurance or corona insurance, then
how much will he be protected,
all his expenses will go out of his mouth, it will
stand like a wall and if there is an inch then
roti, kapda, makaan, PM will be protecting, due to which they are insured, yes, they have become
basic needs
because it is protecting all the previous three basic
needs and do
you know if there is any
Guru Govind edition then 14 to 15
How much does it cost per day? So let me tell you
that according to news reports it is Rs 2.5 to 3 lakh
if ​​he gets his treatment done in a good
private hospital and Rs 1 lakh
to 1.75 lakh if ​​he gets his treatment done
in a general private hospital, Carva Chauth is a
decent private hospital, so that is the
cost, so leave a small
smile, it will be so good,
whatever the clean expense is, all the expenses will be
covered under it and I will talk about
who should take the meeting shoulder
and who should not take it,
who already has health insurance and
is covered under the Kovind and who should take it,
everyone should take it because you
know about Vinod Singh, how it
spreads, I will tell you that all the
Kovind insurance is available
on Flipkart, Paytm, Mobikwik and or
on the phone, if you want to take it, then
definitely watch this video, I am going to discuss with all your Kovind plans at midnight, is it a
spoon type
insurance, is it time
questions, then you will know in this video
if you are online  If you are
thinking of taking insurance for vinegar then
before this I have made a video on
how to buy insurance for corona virus, in that I have
told you how to buy it on the phone and from Mobikwik and the terms and conditions, then you can watch the video,
in this video I will make a video on Flipkart and Paytm, those who will
talk about it, so
let's start, hello friends,
I am worried, you see, desi consumer, first of all
if I talk about there are two types of
insurance, one is the previous one and the other is the
non-fiction one, in which if a
person gets corona, then he tests
positive, then he will get the same amount for which he got insurance at one time
and the other is the non-fiction one in which he will get
life insurance claim, that means if a
person is positive, then whatever
expenses he has for the last 15 days, whatever expenses he has for 30 days,
you will get that claim and for the
coming seven days or 30 days,
he will get that entire claim, so in this way you will get the claim, so
I have made a chart, so I will tell you  Let me
tell you, in this I have all the Tom
and Jerry, let's first talk about it, then it
is available at two places Flipkart and
Paytm, there are three available on Flipkart, in
which only one is the back and two are not the back, let
me tell you about the sides, first let's
talk about the back and all the insurances available on Paytm are all
the back, so let's see,
after that let's talk about Flipkart and Paytm, let's talk about the
icy winds, so the
price on Flipkart is 159 and the one which
is of 25 thousand rupees, if it
turns out to be positive, then if I talk about Paytm, there are
four plans, although there are a lot, I have
written four lines, in this the price is
first 220 ₹5 in which there is Rs.25000 Kalim,
so here you can see that the Flipkart one
is cheaper, if you
want to buy Rs.25000 Kalim, then if I talk about the
top plan available on Happy Day, in which the
force is ₹2 in which there is 50,000  The
claim is of 90% of this, in which Rs 1 lakh was claimed
in the previous one and Rs 1805 of
this was claimed for Rs 4 lakh after last month. Your
terms and conditions are such that if I talk about the
conditions for this,
on Flipkart a person between 18 years to 75 years can
take Flipkart Sale, anyone
above that cannot take insurance below that and
if I talk about Paytm a 3 month old
baby and a person up to 60 years can take insurance, the
next condition given is that there should
not be any travelling free forex trading,
what is the condition on the comment, from 31st December 2019 onwards
when you take this insurance, there should
not be any immediate travelling here, and
if I talk about Paytm, there should
not be any point travelling in the last 45 days when you are taking these insurance,
now let's talk about the waiting period, there is a
waiting period of 15 days everywhere, so that
means after 15 days when you are taking the insurance, the
insurance will start and
then in that 15 days  If anyone's combination
is positive then the claim will not be available and if we talk about
cancellation then you
can cancel on Flipkart and you will get a full refund
but I have
come within the day, let me pencil in the same,
if I talk about cancellation not allowed on Paytm
and if we talk about validity then it is worth
mentioning that there is good
validity everywhere, there should be a test, if you
take the patient to the hospital, wherever you are getting the
test done, it should be government authorized, so
this is the terms and
conditions of the explanation, for fee claim and
loan, let me tell you one more decision in the last, the back
insurance is
expensive and the loan back plan is
cheap, so now let me
talk about the plan which is not fixed plan, the
price of Flipkart plan is first for
511 in which there is a claim of one lakh rupees, the
second one is twelve weeks and
in Delhi it is three lakh rupees, the validity of your plan is one
year, it is one year everywhere, age 18  A
person of 18 years can buy this
new condition on Flipkart. This note is about the previous Malik plan
and if we talk about foreign travelling then there should
not be any foreign entry in the last 30 days.
This condition was for the
police. This is non-fiction
and the waiting period is 15 days. And
cancellation is a robbery here, but nothing was
told about the record. Perhaps you will get a
refund of some amount. And if we talk about the
expenses, how will you get it, then you can clear all the
expenses on room rent and ICU.
You can
claim up to the limit. Whatever the person who tests
positive does in the past days will be included.
Claims will be made and whatever expenses are going to be incurred in the coming seven days can be
cleared.
If we talk about one percent of the
amount of the patient, which is one percent, which you
can claim in the ambulance expenses.
So these were the terms and
conditions that I told you about non-fiction which
you can buy on Flipkart. Then there is only
one plan of it.  It is on Flipkart and the rest is
plain and there are multiples on Paytm,
so if I talk about it, you take a screenshot of it
and see the terms and conditions carefully, from
where you want to buy, if you
want to buy then I will write all the tensions in it, the
rest can be left, that is
when you go to buy, you will come to know, it is a
vacation, talk about how to buy,
Paytm also, open the Paytm app,
here you will get this Benedict card
or you can search and you will
search for it, all the plans will be sold to you,
whatever you want to buy, select them,
click on terms and conditions,
make a profit and buy them by making the payment, after 15 days
it will be activated and talk about
how to buy from Flipkart, open the Flipkart app,
there you will see Jatin,
subscribe on the left side, then you will
see some program of insurance,
click there, after clicking on it you will
see life insurance and
click on your health insurance, after that all the
three insurances will appear in front of you, the
first one, the last card, the
other two given are space ones, so simply
Select the app you want to buy
and make the payment and it will be
activated after 15 days and
how to claim, you will get the number in their terms and conditions
and
you can claim from there by going to the email ID and by
clicking on it you can buy only one app from one account,
which one did I like the bathroom, I liked the
non-fiction one
because it is cheaper and the
claim is also higher and which one did I like the plant, there is
a plan available on Mobikwik
which is around Rs 700 in which
we get this for Rs 1.5 lakh, so
I liked the country channel of Flipkart, the
same condition is there on Mobikwik as the previous one, the
rest you can watch the video, the link is
in the description, till then that's all in this video,
if you liked the video,
like the video because it gives motivation to
make such videos in future, so
if you are new to the channel then subscribe
because I make my own videos, so you will get
related to consumer benefits
in some such video, till then ok
chata baba  Is